gametz.com 2003-06-01

# Game Trading Zone - Privacy

### Privacy Statement for Game Trading Zone

Game Trading Zone has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Game Trading Zone. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, detect rules violations and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). Users may opt out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Other information related to listing and ratings is also recorded. 

This site contains links to other sites. **Game Trading Zone** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms and forum message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Whispered message within the chat room may be viewed and acted upon by site moderators in order to enforce the rules of the site. 

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All accounts have passwords and the server itself is locked down a tight as possible (there are very few ways to access it). Additionally, all data at this site is backed-up daily. 

### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

Users may freeze or request deletion of their account if they wish to no longer receive communication from GameTZ and no longer use our service. 

  * You can send email to [moderators@gametz.com](mailto:moderators@gametz.com)
  * You can visit the following URL: <http://gametz.com/?A=My+Account>

In either case, any GameTZ user has the option of removing their personal information from the GameTZ database by direct request. 

### Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  * visit <http://gametz.com/?A=My+Account>
  * Generally any of the My ... pages give you the ability to edit your information here. 

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact William Marrs Game Trading Zone moderators@gametz.com

Copyright © 1996-2003 Kenyon Hill LLC. All rights reserved.  
[Take our Poll](http://survey.burstmedia.com/cgi-win/client.exe?readers,welcome,ad5418a,2000) \- [Privacy Statement](http://gametz.com/Privacy.html) \- [Subscribe](http://gametz.com/Subscribe.html)
